现在另一个非常重要的技能
Now another very important skill
当您成为 Web 开发人员时，您将需要
that you will need as you become a web developer
就是调试自己的代码，以防万一问问题
is to debug your own code and to ask questions in case
你无法解决某些问题。
that you cannot solve certain problems.
所以在编程中，
So in programming,
我们说一个错误基本上是一个错误或错误。
we say that a bug is basically an error or a mistake.
所以基本上调试我们的代码意味着查找和修复
And so basically debugging our code means finding and fixing
代码中的错误。
errors in code.
好的。
All right.
所以现在让我们假设您的代码中有一些错误
So let's now pretend that there is some error in your code
在 HTML 中，最常见的错误，
and in HTML, the most common error,
所以最常见的错误是某些元素
so the most common bug that occurs, is that some elements
保持未关闭状态。
remain unclosed.
所以即使使用 VS Code 也很容易发生这种情况
So that can easily happen even with VS Code
自动为我们关闭元素，
automatically closing elements for us,
但有时仍然使用复制粘贴
but still sometimes with copy paste
或发生的其他一些事情。
or with some other things that happen.
有时我们最终会删除这些结束标签
Sometimes we end up deleting these closing tags
然后可能会出现一些错误。
and then some error might appear.
所以让我们说，出于某种原因，
So let's say that for some reason,
我们从来没有在这里关闭强元素。
we never closed the strong element here.
然后我们的页面将如下所示。
And then our page is going to look like this.
当然，对于这个例子，
And of course, for this example,
我们需要假装我们不知道这个错误，对吧？
we need to pretend that we don't know about this bug, right?
无论如何，这没有任何意义。
Anyway, this doesn't make any sense.
所以如果我们只是引入了一个错误
So if we just introduced a bug
然后我们渲染我们的页面，
and then we render our page,
然后突然之间，我们的页面看起来像这样，对吧？
then all of a sudden, our page looks like this, right?
这可能有点吓人
And this might be a little bit scary
因为您查看您的页面，它看起来非常错误。
because you look at your page and it looks very wrong.
这不是你想要的，对吧？
This is not what you intended, right?
那么如何解决这个问题呢？
So how to fix this?
好吧，在这种情况下，它实际上非常简单。
Well, in this case, it is actually very simple.
您需要做的就是在此处查看此结果。
All you need to do is to take a look at this result here.
所以在这个页面，
So at this page,
并实际找出错误开始的地方。
and actually figure out where the bug started.
所以这里的问题显然是所有的文字都是粗体的，
So the problem here is clearly that all the text is bold,
你不希望它在哪里。
where you don't want it to be.
所以要调试这段代码，
And so to debug this code,
您需要查看代码不是粗体的位置。
you need to look where the code is not bold.
所以在这里，例如，文本不是粗体。
So up here, for example, the text is not bold.
所以这个错误必须出现在这个下面的某个地方。
And so the bug must appear somewhere below this.
那么这里的这个是大胆的，
Then this one here is bold,
但这仅仅是因为它是一个h2。
but that's simply because it's an h2.
然后在这里你会看到一些不是粗体的文本。
Then here you see some more text that is also not bold.
然后从这里突然之间，一切都是大胆的。
And then from here on all of a sudden, everything is bold.
所以这意味着你的错误必须在这里的某个地方。
And so that means that your bug must be somewhere here.
然后你可以回到你的 HTML
And so then you can move back to your HTML
请注意，哦，您没有关闭此元素。
and notice that, oh, you did not close this element.
然后很简单。
And then it's very simple.
你只要来这里，关闭你的元素，
You just come here, close your element,
给它一个保存，你回来了。
give it a save and you're back.
当然，同样的事情也会发生
And the same can of course happen
在所有其他类型的元素上。
on all other kinds of elements.
所以让我们说由于某种原因你覆盖了
So let's say for some reason you overrode
这个结束标签在这里。
this closing tag here.
然后你再看一遍，
Then you'll take a look, and again,
一切都突然变得大胆，也变得更大更蓝了。
everything is suddenly bold and also bigger and blue.
所以可能立即从颜色和粗体文本中，
And so maybe immediately from the color and the bold text,
你可以看到这现在看起来像一个 h3。
you can see that this now looks like a the h3.
再次，您可以使用您的代码，
So again, you can then come to your code,
注意有一个错误并修复它。
notice that there is a bug and fix it.
现在，很常见的错误之一
Now, one of the bugs that is quite common
是不是例如，在这里，你关闭李
is that for example, here, you close the Li
并将内容留在外面。
and the leave the content outside.
所以像这样。
So something like this.
然后当你检查你的页面时，
00:03:37,810 -->00:03:41,010
有些东西看起来很不对劲，对吧？
And then as you check your page,
something looks very off, right?
但话又说回来，这只是去的问题
But then again, it is just a matter of going
到 HTML 中与此问题对应的位置，
to the place in the HTML that corresponds to this problem,
然后弄清楚发生了什么。
and then figure out what happened.
所以这个案子，很清楚
So this case, that's pretty clear
你有一个额外的关闭李。
you have an extra closing Li.
所以只要关闭它，我们就会回到安全的地方。
So just close that and we are back to safety here.
现在，如果这发生在一个更大的元素中怎么办？
Now, what if this happens in like a bigger element?
所以让我们在旁边说。
So let's say here in the aside.
如果我们删除它，那么错误
If we delete this, then the error
可能不是那么明显。
might not be that apparent.
所以你看，它并不那么明显。
So you see, it's not that apparent.
所发生的只是这里的文本
All that happened is that this text here
突然在这个旁观元素里面。
is suddenly inside of this aside element.
所以现在假设您在代码中创建了这个错误
So now imagine that you created this bug in your code
很早，甚至在你真正之前
very early on, even before you actually
开始写CSS。
started writing the CSS.
所以在那种情况下，你从来没有注意到
And so in that case, you never noticed
这正在发生。
that this was happening.
然后当你开始编写 CSS 时，
And then as you started writing the CSS,
你突然注意到这是关闭的，
you suddenly noticed that this is off,
但你真的不记得写过 HTML。
but you don't really remember writing the HTML.
所以你不确定这里可能有什么问题。
So you're not sure what might be wrong here.
在这种情况下，这是一个很好的解决方案
And so a great solution in that case
是实际使用 HTML 验证器工具。
is to actually use an HTML validator tool.
所以这基本上可以让你看到
So that will basically allow you to see
您的 HTML 是否有效。
if your HTML is valid or not.
所以要做到这一点，让我们在这里复制所有代码。
So to do that, let's copy all the code here.
至少我认为这是最简单的方法。
At least that I think is the easiest way of doing this.
那么这里我们需要谷歌，HTML验证器
Then here we need to Google, HTML validator
然后通常应该是第一个结果，
and then usually it should be this very first result,
但我也会有一个指向这个 HTML 验证器的链接
but I will also have a link to this HTML validator
正如我之前向您展示的那样，在我的资源页面上。
on my resources page as I showed you before.
所以这里我们可以通过引入一个URI来进行验证。
So here we can validate by introducing a URI.
这就像一个 URL。
So that's something like a URL.
我们可以手动上传文件，
We can manually upload a file,
或者我们可以简单地将刚刚复制的代码粘贴到这里。
or we can simply paste the code that we just copied here.
再说一次，也就是说，我认为最简单的解决方案。
And so again, that is, I think the easiest solution.
所以让我们点击检查
So let's click on check
现在实际上我们有几个错误。
and now actually we have a couple of errors.
所以不仅仅是我们正在寻找的那个，
So not just the one that we were looking for,
但你会看到这里实际上是
but you'll see that down here actually is
把那个未封闭的元素放在一边。
that unclosed element aside.
这就是我们故意引入的错误。
So that is the bug that we just on purpose introduced.
所以让我们在这里解决这个问题。
So let's fix that here.
现在，好吧。
Now, all right.
然后在这里我们有另一个错误是看到结束标签div，
Then here we have another error which is end tag div seen,
但它们是开放元素。
but they were open elements.
所以这个错误其实和这个有关，
So this error is actually related to this one,
这在验证器中很常见。
and this is quite common to see in a validator.
所以代码中的一个错误
So that one error in the code
实际上然后在这里创建一些倍数，好吗？
actually then create some multiple right here, okay?
所以这两个被我们刚刚在这里所做的修复了，
So these two were fixed by what we just did here,
但是在这里，显然我们还有其他一些错误
but then here, apparently we have some other errors
在我们的代码中。
in our code.
因此，让我们实际解决这些问题。
So let's actually fixed those.
所以在第 131 行，我们有重复的属性宽度。
So in line 131, we have the duplicate attribute width.
所以让我们解决这个问题。
So let's fix that.
事实上，这是真的。
And actually that's true.
所以我们有宽度，然后又是宽度，
So we have width, and then width again,
当然这应该是高度。
and of course this should be height.
这么高，像这样。
So height, like this.
最后还有一个。
And then finally there is yet another one.
所以在第 137 行，属性高度是不允许的。
So in line 137, attribute height not allowed.
实际上这里的问题是拼写错误。
And actually the problem here is that this is misspelled.
所以这是一个愚蠢的错误。
So that's a stupid error.
所以不是这样，而是像这样。
So it's not th but ht like this.
所以你看，实际上，甚至在故意之前，
So you see that actually, even before on purpose,
引入一个错误，我们一直有无效的 HTML。
introducing a bug, we had invalid HTML all along.
所以现在我再次复制它。
So now I'm copying it again.
那么在这里我将指挥或控制一个
So then here I will command or control a
选择所有内容，将其删除并再次粘贴。
to select everything, delete it and paste it again.
然后检查，现在我们没有要显示的错误或警告。
Then check and now we have no errors or warnings to show.
好的，这就是 HTML 验证器。
Okay, so that is the HTML validator.
所以，一个非常有用的工具，
So, a very useful tool,
但现在让我向你展示另一个工具，
but let me now actually show you another tool,
这是一个 div 检查器和一个 div 检查器
which is a div checker and a div checker
对比较您自己的代码很有帮助
can be very helpful to compare your own code
使用我在视频中实际编码的代码。
with my code that I actually code here in the videos.
所以如果你遇到任何问题
So in case you run into any problem
你的页面看起来和我的不一样，
where your page looks different than mine,
您的代码可能有问题。
probably something is wrong in your code.
所以在那种情况下，
And so in that situation,
基本上，您可以自动将您的代码与我的代码进行比较。
you can compare your code automatically to mine, basically.
所以让我们说，出于某种原因，
So let's say that for some reason,
此处不使用 a 元素，而是使用链接。
instead of using the a element here, you use link.
链接在这里没有任何意义，
And link doesn't make any sense here,
但是，使用锚点，我们实际上是在创建超链接。
but well, with anchors, we are actually creating hyperlinks.
所以出于某种原因，你可能犯了一个错误
And so for some reason, you might have made a mistake
of，而不是使用 a，使用链接，
of, instead of using a, using link,
因为你可能认为
because you might've thought
这就是创建链接的原因。
that this is what creates links.
所以现在不知何故你的代码在这里不可点击
And so now somehow your code here is not clickable
它是黑色而不是蓝色。
and it's black instead of blue.
实际上让我们回到这里的 CSS
And actually let's go back to our CSS here
并在导航中删除这段代码
and in the nav remove this piece of code
我们在上一个视频中添加的，对吧？
that we added in the last video, right?
但无论如何，现在让我们实际比较一下这段代码
But anyway, now let's actually compare this code
用我的代码。
with my code.
因此，使用本节中的最终代码。
So with the final code in this section.
所以让我们像这样搜索 div 检查器，
So let's search for div checker like this,
然后你可以简单地使用 divchecker.com。
and then you can simply use divchecker.com.
因此，您将在这里放置您的代码。
So here you will put your code.
同样，命令或控制 a，然后复制，然后粘贴。
So again, command or control a, then copy, then paste.
现在在这边，
And now here on this side,
您需要其他代码或实际上相反。
you need the other code or actually the other way around.
所以在这里你想要原版。
So here you want the original.
所以让我们删除它，在这里你更改的文本。
So let's delete that and here your changed text.
现在让我们来看看您下载的代码。
And so let's now come to the code that you downloaded.
所以这个存储库，然后我在这里有最终的文件夹。
So this repository, and then I have the final folder here.
这就是您可以使用此代码的目的。
And so this is what you can use this code for.
因此，将其与您自己的代码进行比较。
So to compare it with your own code.
所以我们在 CSS 基础的这一部分
So we are in this section of the CSS fundamentals
我们对索引感兴趣。
and we're interested in the index.
所以为了打开它，
And so in order to open this up,
我们可以非常简单地将它拖到 VS Code 图标上
we can very simply drag it onto the VS Code icon
在菜单栏中。
here in the menu bar.
这就是本节的最终代码。
And so this is, basically the final code of this section.
所以，再一次，选择一切，复制它，
So, so again, selecting everything, copying it,
然后我可以把它贴在这里。
then I can paste that here.
然后某个地方应该有
And then somewhere there should be
查找不同的按钮。
the find different button.
所以当你看这个视频的时候，
So by the time you are watching this video,
这个界面可能看起来有点不同，
this interface might look a little bit different,
但基本思想应该仍然存在。
but the basic idea should still be there.
你有两个文本框
That you have two text boxes
然后一些按钮来比较它们。
and then some button to compare them.
所以只需单击它，然后您就会看到差异
So just click that and then you see the differences
很好地标记在这里。
nicely marked in here.
所以在原版中，我们当然有 a 元素
So in the original, of course we have the a element
而你，由于某种原因有链接，好吗？
while you, for some reason had the link, okay?
在这种情况下，这是唯一的区别
And in this case that's the only difference
或者实际上这里是其他一些。
or actually here is some other one.
所以结束标签和这里只是结束。
So the closing tag and here is just closing.
所以让我也真正解决这个问题。
So let me actually fix that as well.
所以在这里，当然应该是一个，
So here, of course it should be a,
让我们把它放回去
let's put that back
这里的内容也有问题。
and in here there's also something wrong in content.
所以这里的结束标签，应该是结束标签。
So closing tag here, it should be the closing tag.
看看还有没有别的
Let's see if there is something else,
但是啊，是的，这是我们刚刚解决的这些错误。
but ah, yeah, here are these bugs that we just solved also.
所以以前我们有两次宽度，对吧？
So previously we had width twice, right?
所以我们已经解决了这个问题。
And so we fixed that already.
所以在这里我们很好。
And so here we are good.
这在以前是错误的。
And this was wrong previously.
所以在最终的文件中，它实际上仍然是错误的，好吗？
So in the final file, it was actually still wrong, okay?
但除此之外，仅此而已。
But besides that, that's it.
好的。
Okay.
然后在这里，我们可以再次访问
Then down here, we have access again to
该文本，以便我们可以在此处进行一些更改。
that text so we can do some changes here.
所以让我再介绍几个，
So let me just introduce a couple more,
这样我们就可以看到当时的样子。
just so we could see how that looks like then.
所以这里的这个李，假设我们没有以某种方式关闭它。
So this Li here, let's say we didn't close this somehow.
假设在页脚内部，
Let's say that here inside of the footer,
我们实际上不是关闭了页脚，而是出于某种原因关闭了页眉。
we actually closed not footer, but header for some reason.
好吧，找个不同的。
Okay, find a difference.
然后在这里你看到它看起来非常不同。
And then here you see that it looks very different.
所以即使你只有空行，
So even if you have just empty lines,
它仍然会显示在 div 检查器中。
it will still show up here in the div checker.
对？
Right?
这就是我们刚刚介绍的所有更改。
So that's all the changes that we just introduced.
现在，好吧，太好了。
Now, okay, great.
所以 div 检查器和 HTML 验证器
So div checker and HTML validators
是调试 HTML 代码的两个非常有用的工具。
are two extremely helpful tools to debug your HTML code.
但是现在让我们真正开始使用 CSS，因为还有
But now let's go actually to CSS because there are also
那里可能发生的一些潜在错误。
some potential bugs that might happen there.
现在，CSS 中最常见的错误来源之一
Now, one of the most common sources of bugs in CSS
是选择器之间的一些冲突。
are some conflicts between selectors.
所以让我们再次在这里选择这些链接，
So let's select these links here once again,
请记住，它们在导航内部，
and keep in mind that they are inside of the nav,
这是主标题的内部。
which is inside of the main header.
好的。
Okay.
所以我们在这里有一个导航链接，但出于某种原因，
So we have the nav a link here, but for some reason,
假设我们也选择了这些链接
let's imagine that we selected these links also
在其他地方，然后在那里编辑一些不同的样式。
somewhere else and then edit some different style there.
所以让我们说中间的某个地方
So let's say somewhere here in the middle
其余的代码，
of the rest of the code,
在这里我们写了一个不同的选择器。
and here we wrote a different selector.
所以假设我们在这里写了主标题
So let's say that here we wrote main header
然后在导航里面，然后在里面
and then inside of that the nav and then inside that the a
像这样，在这里我们将颜色设置为红色。
like this, and here we set the color actually to red.
好的，但我们仍然希望我们的颜色是蓝色的。
Okay, but we still want our color to be blue.
但是现在如果我们重新加载它，那么我们的文本实际上是红色的。
But now if we reload this, then our text is actually red.
所以我们有两个选择器，
So we have two selectors,
它们都定义了颜色并且它们都适用。
which both define the color and they both apply.
所以如果在你写这个之前，只有在你之后
And so if before you wrote this and only later you
然后写了这段代码
then wrote this piece of code
并希望文本实际上是蓝色的，
and wanted the texts actually to be blue,
那你可能不理解
then you might not be understanding
这里实际发生了什么。
what actually happens here.
虽然颜色实际上并不是这里的完美示例。
While the color is actually not the perfect example here.
所以让我们用边距顶部来代替。
So let's play instead with the margin top.
所以让我们说，出于某种原因，
So let's say that for some reason,
您将链接的边距顶部定义为 100 像素，
you defined the margin top to be 100 pixels for the link,
但过了一会儿，又一次，
but then a bit later, again,
你把这条规则写在你真正想要的地方
you write this rule here where you actually only want
边距顶部为 10 像素。
the margin top to be 10 pixels.
所以你正在写这个规则，然后你给它一个save.
So you are writing this rule, then you give it a save.
突然之间，它看起来像这样。
And all of a sudden it looks like this.
所以你有100个像素。
So you have 100 pixels.
那么发生了什么？
So what is happening?
好吧，让我们检查一下，好吧，
Well, let's inspect and well,
您会看到这两个选择器当然都适用。
you see that both of these selectors apply of course.
所以这两个规则。
So both of the rules.
但实际适用的边距顶部
But the margin top that does actually apply
这是这个更长的选择器中的一个吗？
is this one here in this longer selector.
所以根据经验，
So as a rule of thumb,
除了我们之前已经学过的规则
besides the rules that we already learned before
关于选择器优先级，
about selector priority,
如果一个选择器比另一个复杂得多，
if one selector is way more complex than the other,
然后很多时候它实际上是更复杂的
then many times it's actually the more complex one
得到应用。
that gets applied.
好的。
Okay.
所以这就是为什么我之前也告诉过你
And so that's why I also told you before
您应该避免编写这样的选择器。
that you should avoid writing a selector like this.
所以一个非常复杂的。
So a very complex one.
所以保持你的选择器简单，就像这个，
So keep your selector simple, like this one,
这样就可以避免产生这样的错误。
and that will then avoid creating bugs like this.
好的。
Okay.
现在，从技术上讲，
Now, technically here,
如果我们看一下选择器的特殊性，
if we take a look at the selector specificity,
你看，它有 1,2 对吗？
you see it, that it has 1,2 right?
所以记住0、1、2。
So memorize that 0, 1, 2.
这里我们有 0、2、2。
And here we have 0, 2, 2.
所以这些数字更大
And so these numbers are larger
因此这是实际应用的。
and therefore this is the one that actually gets applied.
现在我之前提到过，
Now I mentioned before,
不用担心特异性
not to worry about specificity
因为那太复杂了，
because that gets too complex,
但基本上数字越高，
but basically the higher the numbers,
选择器应用的越多。
the more that selector apply.
好的？
All right?
所以不要写这样的选择器
So don't write selectors like this
而是保持低特异性。
and instead keep their specificity low.
好的。
Okay.
如果你遵守我给你看的规则
And if you follow the rules that I showed you
关于选择器的优先级，那么你应该没问题。
about the priority of selectors, then you should be fine.
另一个可能发生的常见问题
Another common problem that might happen
是因为某种原因你拼错了一个属性名称
is that for some reason you misspelled a property name
这一直在发生。
and that happens all the time.
所以让我们说，而不是正确的，你写了这个，
So let's say that instead of right, you wrote this,
然后你给它一个保存。
then you give it a save.
当然元素没有定位
And of course the element is not positioned
你期望它在哪里。
where you expected it to be.
所以在那种情况下，
So in that case,
简单的事情就是检查那个元素
the simple thing to do is simply to inspect that element
然后看看那里发生了什么。
and then check out what happened there.
现在在像这样的伪元素的情况下，
Now in the case of a pseudo element like this,
你实际上必须点击这里
you will actually have to then click here
打开元素本身，
to open the element itself,
然后从那里你可以选择伪元素。
and then from there you can select the pseudo element.
然后你可以简单地查看这里的属性
And then you can simply check out the properties here
然后你会在这里找到这个图标，
and you will then find this icon here,
这意味着未知的属性名称。
which means unknown property name.
因此，您将立即知道
And so from that, you will immediately know
你在这里拼错了一些东西。
that here you misspelled something.
那么你来到你的代码，修复它
So then you come here to your code, fix that
你可以再去一次。
and you're a good to go again.
所以这个也比你想象的更常见。
So this one is also more common than you thought.
所以做我刚刚在这里做的事情
And so doing what I just did here
总是一个好主意。
is always a good idea.
总的来说，这也总是一个好主意
And in general, it is also always a good idea
总是试验这段代码
to always experiment with this code
您在开发工具中拥有的
that you have here in the dev tools
并玩弄它。
and play around with it.
例如，在此处调整值。
And for example, tweak values here.
因此，而不是，例如，
So instead of, for example,
在代码中尝试使用 h2 字体大小，
experimenting with the h2 font size here in the code,
你可以简单地来这里这个值，点击它，
you can simply come here to this value, click it,
然后在你的键盘上，你可以使用向上和向下键，
and then on your keyboard, you can use the up and down keys,
就像这里所说的那样。
just like it says here.
实际上，在那个工具提示中也是如此。
Actually, so in that tool tip.
所以有了这个，你可以在现实生活中看到这些价值观是如何变化的
So with this, you can see real life how these values changed
你也可以使用 shift 和 up 和 down，
and you can also use shift and up and down,
然后它将以 10 的步长递增。
and then it will increment in steps of 10.
所以这非常非常有帮助。
So this is very, very helpful.
我在实验时一直这样做
I do this all the time when I'm experimenting
有不同的价值观，好吧。
with different values, okay.
如果出于某种原因你真的不知何故
And if for some reason you somehow really
无法修复您的代码。
cannot fix your code.
然后，当然，再次，您可以使用 div 检查器
Then of course, again, you can use the div checker
将您的 CSS 代码与您的 CSS 代码进行比较
to compare your CSS code with the one
我在视频中展示的。
that I show in the video.
所以该部分的最终代码，
So the final code of the section,
那是在存储库中
that is in the repository
我刚才给你看了。
that I just showed you before.
现在，最后，我看到初学者犯的一个错误
Now, finally, one error that I see beginners make
一直是没有正确链接CSS文件
all the time is to not correctly link the CSS file
首先。
in the first place.
所以请记住，这发生在此链接中。
So remember that, that happens up here in this link.
有时由于某些原因，
And sometimes for some reasons,
学生弄乱了 CSS 文件的路径。
students mess up the path to the CSS file.
那也是因为有时我们可能想把这个
That's also because sometimes we might want to put this
到不同的文件夹。
into a different folder.
所以就像我们对图像所做的那样。
So just like we did with the images.
然后你需要正确，当然，写路径
And then you need to correctly, of course, write the path
与此 HTML 文件有关。
in relation to this HTML file.
因此，如果您的页面根本没有应用任何 CSS，
So in case that no CSS at all is applied to your page,
那么你需要检查的第一件事
then the first thing that you need to check
是这里的链接是否正确。
is if this link here is correct.
因此，如果您的样式表正确链接到您的 HTML。
So if your style sheet was correctly linked to your HTML.
好的？
Okay?
所以这就是你修复一些最常见的错误的方法
So this is how you fix some of the most common bugs
在 HTML 和 CSS 中。
in HTML and CSS.
但是如果由于某种原因你真的真的无法修复
But if for some reason you really, really cannot fix
您发现的任何错误，
any of the bugs that you found,
甚至使用我刚刚向您展示的所有工具
even using all of the tools that I just showed you
在这个视频中，当然你可以问一个问题
in this video, then of course you can ask a question
在我刚刚向您展示的平台之一中。
in one of the platforms that I just showed you.
特别是在 Stack Overflow 上，
And in particular on Stack Overflow,
或者你也可以在这里发布一个新问题
or you can also post a new question here
在 Udemy 问答中。
in the Udemy Q and A.
现在重要的是你总是发帖
Now what matters here is that you always post
首先将所有代码写入代码笔。
all of your code to a code pen first.
因此，不要复制并粘贴所有代码
So instead of a copy and paste all your code
到 Stack Overflow 或 Udemy Q and A，
to Stack Overflow or into the Udemy Q and A,
请让帮助你的人轻松一点。
please make it easy for the person who will help you.
而是将所有代码粘贴到代码笔中。
And instead paste all your code into a code pen.
所以我们已经使用了代码笔来应对挑战，
So we have already used code pen for the challenges,
但只是为了确定，好吧，它现在在哪里？
but just to make sure, well, where is it now?
哦，这里。
Oh, here.
所以开始编码，
So start coding,
或者你可以只写斜线笔
or you can just write slash pen
然后再一次，抓住你所有的代码，
and then again, grab all your code,
把 HTML 和你所有的 CSS 都放在这里。
put a tear in the HTML and then all your CSS right here.
如果你有 JavaScript，你也可以把它放在这里，
And in case you have JavaScript, you can also put it here,
然后你会保存它，你需要一个帐户。
then you'll save it for which you will need an account.
然后你只需复制 URL 并粘贴它
And then you just copy the URL and paste it
到 Stack Overflow 或 Udemy Q and A 部分。
either to Stack Overflow or to the Udemy Q and A section.
好的？
Okay?
现在，对。
Now, right.
我认为这就是基本技能
And I think that's it about the basic skills
调试和提问。
of debugging and asking questions.
所以当然，调试可以比这更深入，
So of course, debugging can go a lot deeper than just this,
但现在，我只是想给你一个概述
but for now, I just wanted to give you an overview
调试是什么以及它是如何工作的。
of what debugging is and how it works.
现在结束这一节，
And now to wrap up this section,
让我们继续构建我们的编码挑战
let's continue building our coding challenge
我们一直在构建的，在下一个视频中。
that we have been building ,in the next video.